<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Terminal.</string>
    <string name="app_name_uppercase">THE TERMINAL.</string>

    <string name="copyright">Part of the Terminal News &amp; Media Syndicate. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="edition_online">ONLINE EDITION</string>

    <string name="article_author_by">By</string>
    <string name="label_staff_reporter_of">Staff Reporter of</string>

    <string name="news_org_the_terminal">The Terminal</string>
    <string name="news_org_u">Organization</string>

    <string name="article_author_u">Full Name</string>
    <string name="article_author_1">Sarah Monroe</string>
    <string name="article_author_2">Lillian Abadi</string>
    <string name="article_author_3">Finsbury Bowes</string>

    <string name="article_u_image_description">Image Description</string>
    <string name="article_1_image_description">Dr. Wallace Breen</string>
    <string name="article_2_image_description">WITNESSING THE UNKNOWABLE: No pattern has been discerned for where or when a portal will open.</string>
    <string name="article_3_image_description">Source: Terminal Data</string>

    <string name="article_headline_1">Unlikely Negotiator Of Peace Garners Ill Will And Distrust As Well As Praise</string>
    <string name="article_headline_2">\"Portal\" Storm Continues</string>
    <string name="article_headline_3">An Astronomical Downturn</string>
    <string name="article_headline_4">Resonant Energy Fields Disrupt Black Mesa Protocols</string>
    <string name="article_headline_5">Unexpected Portal Anomalies Force Security Response Team</string>
    <string name="article_headline_6">Scientific Containment Breach Sparks Experimental Chaos Nearby</string>
    <string name="article_headline_7">Strange Atmospheric Fluctuations Delay Military Reinforcement Plans</string>
    <string name="article_headline_8">Dimensional Rifts Reveal Hidden Opposing Force Operations</string>
    <string name="article_headline_9">Decay Experimentation Sparks Controversy Among Senior Researchers</string>
    <string name="article_headline_10">Unidentified Aliens Appear Within Confined Laboratory Sectors</string>
    <string name="article_headline_11">Emergency Broadcast Signals Alert Civilian Populations Instantly</string>
    <string name="article_headline_12">Critical Infrastructure Fails Under Combined Portal And Shockwaves</string>
    <string name="article_headline_13">Time Distortions Affect Personnel During Security Breach Exercises</string>
    <string name="article_headline_14">Unexpected Toxic Cloud Spreads Across Lower Research Chambers</string>
    <string name="article_headline_15">Weaponized Gravity Fields Challenge Conventional Containment Methods</string>
    <string name="article_headline_16">High-Risk Reconnaissance Missions Observe Hostile Alien Patterns</string>
    <string name="article_headline_17">Quantum Instabilities Detected In Sector Seven Laboratories</string>
    <string name="article_headline_18">Biotic Contamination Forces Protocol Update And Evacuation Orders</string>
    <string name="article_headline_19">Security Teams Encounter Unexplained Temporal Phenomena Suddenly</string>
    <string name="article_headline_20">Abnormal Neural Feedback Hinders Operator Response Times</string>
    <string name="article_headline_21">Facility Sensors Report Shadow Entities Moving Between Corridors</string>
    <string name="article_headline_22">Experimental Teleportation Devices Malfunction Under External Stress</string>
    <string name="article_headline_23">Communication Blackouts Disrupt Coordination With Civil Defense Units</string>
    <string name="article_headline_24">Unexpected Civilian Movements Complicate Strategic Containment Plans</string>
    <string name="article_headline_25">Hazardous Waste Leak Exposes Researchers To Unknown Energies</string>
    <string name="article_headline_26">Military Protocols Adjust Rapidly To Multidimensional Threat Scenarios</string>
    <string name="article_headline_27">Automated Defense Turrets Trigger Unexpected Chain Reactions Instantly</string>
    <string name="article_headline_28">Gamma Radiation Surges Delay Experiment Completion And Analysis</string>
    <string name="article_headline_29">Unscheduled Dimensional Shifts Interrupt Long-Term Facility Studies</string>
    <string name="article_headline_30">Strange Auditory Signals Confuse Personnel During Crisis Evaluation</string>

    <string name="article_subheadline_1">Wallace Breen Acknowledges Detractors: \"I\'m Not A Politician, I\'m A Scientist\"</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_2">End to Combine Invasion is No Respite, Experts Warn</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_3">Historic Bubble Bursts Upon Earth\'s Sudden Surrender to Combine</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_4">Unexpected Energy Surges Sweep Across Black Mesa And Cause System Malfunctions: \"Containment Is Critical\" Urged Scientists</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_5">Military Teams Report Anomalous Portal Activity Within Secure Research Labs, Analysts Warn Of Potential Collateral Damage</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_6">High-Priority Containment Breaches Force Personnel Evacuation: Researchers Struggle To Stabilize Experimental Fields Safely</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_7">Strange Temporal Fluctuations Observed During Routine Security Drills, Causing Confusion And Delayed Protocol Response Times</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_8">Opposing Force Units Detected Operating In Unauthorized Sectors: \"Unknown Objectives\" Remain Under Investigation By Command</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_9">Decay Laboratory Experiments Produce Unexpected Results: Senior Scientists Debate Safety Procedures And Future Test Schedules</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_10">Aliens Appearing In Confined Corridors Challenge Both Security And Science Teams, Forcing Immediate Tactical Revisions</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_11">Emergency Broadcast Signals Trigger Civilian Alarm Systems Across Multiple Zones, Prompting Coordination With Military Oversight</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_12">Structural Instabilities Detected In Facility Core Areas After Combined Shockwave And Dimensional Anomalies: Engineers Issue Urgent Warnings</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_13">Personnel Report Experiencing Severe Time Dilation During Security Exercises, Forcing Review Of Standard Operational Procedures</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_14">Toxic Cloud Emerges From Lower Chambers Unexpectedly, Security Teams Scramble To Implement Containment Measures And Evacuations</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_15">Weaponized Gravity Experiments Affect Entire Laboratory Wing, Raising Concerns Over Long-Term Containment Risks And Protocol Safety</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_16">Reconnaissance Missions Reveal Hostile Alien Patterns Moving Rapidly Through Unmonitored Facility Sectors, Requiring Immediate Strategic Analysis</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_17">Quantum Instabilities Observed In Sector Seven Labs Produce Erratic Energy Signatures, Prompting Analytical Teams To Recommend Shutdown</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_18">Biotic Contamination Incident Forces Immediate Protocol Update And Civilian Evacuation: Scientists Warn Of Unpredictable Mutations</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_19">Security Units Encounter Unexpected Temporal Phenomena Affecting Navigation And Communications, Leading To Delayed Containment Measures</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_20">Abnormal Neural Feedback Interferes With Operator Equipment, Complicating Real-Time Decision Making During Critical Laboratory Operations</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_21">Facility Sensors Detect Shadow-Like Entities Moving Between Corridors: Analysts Investigate Potential Threat To Personnel Safety</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_22">Experimental Teleportation Devices Malfunction Under External Stress Conditions, Resulting In Unscheduled Dimensional Shifts And Containment Alerts</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_23">Communication Blackouts Disrupt Coordination Between Civil Defense And Military Units, Prompting Alternative Command Strategies</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_24">Unexpected Civilian Movements Within Secure Facility Sectors Complicate Strategic Containment And Evacuation Planning</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_25">Hazardous Waste Leak Exposes Researchers To Unknown Energies: Laboratory Protocols Reviewed To Prevent Further Incidents</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_26">Military Protocols Adjust Rapidly To Multidimensional Threat Scenarios, Including Portal Surges And Unstable Energy Fields</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_27">Automated Defense Turrets Trigger Unexpected Chain Reactions Across Facility Zones, Requiring Immediate Shutdown And Reset Procedures</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_28">Gamma Radiation Surges Delay Long-Term Experiment Completion, Forcing Scientists To Rethink Testing And Containment Schedules</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_29">Unscheduled Dimensional Shifts Interrupt Facility Studies, Causing Staff Confusion And Requiring Extensive Containment Coordination</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_30">Strange Auditory Signals Detected During Crisis Evaluation, Confusing Personnel And Requiring Immediate Investigation By Security Teams</string>

    <string name="article_1">Breen vectors oscillate between trust echoes, scientific shadows twisting over negotiation spirals, while criticism currents ripple across perception frameworks, praise fragments scatter unpredictably.</string>
    <string name="article_2">Portal vortices hum through city residues, energy loops fracture temporal nodes, storm fragments collide with Combine whispers, anomalous fluxes ripple along corridors of distorted awareness.</string>
    <string name="article_3">Economic pulses shatter into technological echoes, resource shadows meander across unstable conduits, urban waves distort under systemic tremors, citizen fragments drift through cascading downturn spirals.</string>
    <string name="article_4">Resonant energy fields caused unexpected malfunctions across the Black Mesa facility. Scientists scrambled to contain the erratic surges, issuing rapid safety protocols to all departments. Evacuation drills were partially activated, yet some personnel remained unaware of the unfolding anomalies.</string>
    <string name="article_5">Portal anomalies appeared suddenly in secure research sectors, forcing security teams to respond immediately. Equipment failures hindered real-time monitoring, and analysts struggled to predict the full scope of dimensional instability. Several corridors experienced temporary lockdowns while investigations proceeded.</string>
    <string name="article_6">A containment breach within experimental laboratories generated chaotic energy flows. Researchers attempted stabilization procedures while alarm systems signaled irregular power fluctuations. Senior scientists debated immediate shutdowns, weighing potential damage against critical experimental data.</string>
    <string name="article_7">Temporal distortions interfered with routine security drills, delaying standard operating procedures. Personnel reported disorientation, complicating evacuation simulations and emergency communication. Engineers investigated anomalous sensor readings that hinted at external interference from unknown sources.</string>
    <string name="article_8">Opposing Force units were observed conducting unauthorized operations within restricted sectors. Commanders struggled to understand their objectives while coordinating internal responses. Analysts noted patterns suggesting long-term strategic preparation beyond standard facility protocols.</string>
    <string name="article_9">Decay experiments produced unexpected chemical reactions, creating a volatile environment. Senior scientists debated safety measures, emphasizing containment over experimental progression. Emergency protocols were drafted to ensure minimal exposure of staff and equipment.</string>
    <string name="article_10">Alien entities appeared within confined corridors, creating panic among research teams. Security measures were reinforced, and tactical squads responded to contain the unknown intruders. Observers documented unusual behavior, raising questions about intelligence and origin.</string>
    <string name="article_11">Emergency broadcast signals triggered widespread alarms, alerting civilian populations across multiple zones. Military oversight coordinated evacuation efforts while analysts monitored communication failures. Response teams faced challenges adapting to rapidly evolving threat conditions.</string>
    <string name="article_12">Structural instabilities emerged following combined shockwave and dimensional anomalies. Engineers issued warnings as containment fields fluctuated unpredictably. Damage assessments revealed compromised infrastructure in several core laboratory sectors, prompting immediate action.</string>
    <string name="article_13">Personnel experienced severe time dilation during security exercises, affecting navigation and task completion. Researchers documented chronological anomalies, noting correlations with energy surges. Adjustments to standard operating procedures were recommended to mitigate ongoing temporal disruptions.</string>
    <string name="article_14">A toxic cloud unexpectedly emerged from lower chambers, prompting rapid evacuation. Security teams implemented containment measures while researchers donned protective equipment. Preliminary tests indicated chemical properties unlike previous observations, warranting further investigation.</string>
    <string name="article_15">Weaponized gravity experiments impacted entire laboratory wings, raising safety concerns. Structural monitoring detected abnormal stress patterns, and emergency shutdown protocols were engaged. Analysts emphasized cautious progression to prevent further destabilization.</string>
    <string name="article_16">Reconnaissance missions uncovered hostile alien patterns in unmonitored sectors. Teams documented rapid movements and unpredictable behavior, complicating tactical planning. Immediate strategic adjustments were necessary to maintain facility security.</string>
    <string name="article_17">Quantum instabilities in Sector Seven generated erratic energy signatures. Analytical teams recommended temporary shutdowns while monitoring fluctuations. Observed effects included sensor malfunctions and unpredictable field variations.</string>
    <string name="article_18">A biotic contamination incident forced immediate protocol updates. Civilian evacuation orders were issued as scientists assessed mutation risks. Containment procedures were reinforced, emphasizing safety and minimal exposure.</string>
    <string name="article_19">Security personnel encountered temporal phenomena affecting navigation and communications. Delayed containment measures resulted in confusion, requiring adaptive strategies. Analysts reviewed historical data to understand anomaly triggers and patterns.</string>
    <string name="article_20">Abnormal neural feedback disrupted operator equipment, complicating decision-making. Monitoring systems indicated unusual cognitive interference, prompting additional safety protocols. Investigations explored potential external influences causing widespread system irregularities.</string>
    <string name="article_21">Facility sensors detected shadow-like entities traversing corridors. Analysts investigated potential threats to personnel safety while reviewing surveillance footage. Immediate precautionary measures were enacted to prevent further incidents.</string>
    <string name="article_22">Experimental teleportation devices malfunctioned under external stress, producing unplanned dimensional shifts. Containment alerts were triggered as energy flows became unpredictable. Researchers worked rapidly to stabilize experimental fields before escalation.</string>
    <string name="article_23">Communication blackouts disrupted coordination between civil defense and military units. Alternative command strategies were implemented while monitoring attempts to restore network functionality. Analysts emphasized redundancy to maintain operational control.</string>
    <string name="article_24">Unexpected civilian movements within secure sectors complicated containment and evacuation plans. Teams adapted to spontaneous activity while maintaining safety protocols. Observations suggested psychological stress and environmental disorientation contributed to behavior.</string>
    <string name="article_25">Hazardous waste leaks exposed researchers to unknown energies, prompting urgent containment revisions. Laboratory protocols were updated, emphasizing minimal human exposure. Teams performed risk assessments and monitored long-term environmental effects.</string>
    <string name="article_26">Military protocols adapted quickly to multidimensional threat scenarios. Portal surges and unstable energy fields required dynamic response measures. Commanders coordinated tactical units to minimize risk and maintain operational continuity.</string>
    <string name="article_27">Automated defense turrets triggered unexpected chain reactions across facility zones. Immediate shutdown and reset procedures were enacted to prevent equipment damage. Analysts reviewed system designs to reduce future malfunction potential.</string>
    <string name="article_28">Gamma radiation surges delayed experiment completion, forcing reevaluation of testing schedules. Scientists monitored exposure levels while maintaining containment protocols. Observed effects included equipment instability and procedural adjustments.</string>
    <string name="article_29">Unscheduled dimensional shifts disrupted facility studies, causing staff confusion. Containment coordination required continuous adjustment, and analysts documented irregular phenomena. Researchers reported increased temporal disorientation among personnel.</string>
    <string name="article_30">Strange auditory signals detected during crisis evaluation confused personnel. Immediate investigation by security teams was necessary, revealing unpredictable patterns. Analysts emphasized monitoring to ensure operational readiness and safety.</string>
    <string name="label_read_less">Read Less</string>
    <string name="label_read_more">Read More</string>
</resources>