<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Terminal.</string>

    <string name="snackbar_access_denied">Access Denied</string>

    <string name="copyright">Part of the Terminal News &amp; Media Syndicate. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="edition_online">ONLINE EDITION</string>

    <string name="label_by">By</string>
    <string name="label_staff_reporter_of">Staff Reporter of</string>
    <string name="label_read_more">Read More</string>

    <string name="news_org_example">The GPT Times</string>
    <string name="article_author_example">Chat GPT</string>
    <string name="article_image_caption_example">Image caption</string>

    <string name="news_org_the_terminal">The Terminal</string>

    <string name="article_author_1">Sarah Monroe</string>
    <string name="article_author_2">Lillian Abadi</string>
    <string name="article_author_3">Finsbury Bowes</string>

    <string name="article_image_caption_1">Dr. Wallace Breen</string>
    <string name="article_image_caption_2">WITNESSING THE UNKNOWABLE: No pattern has been discerned for where or when a portal will open.</string>
    <string name="article_image_caption_3">Source: Terminal Data</string>

    <string name="article_url_1_3">https://store.steampowered.com/app/546560/HalfLife_Alyx/</string>

    <string name="ad_title_1">REALITY DEFINED.</string>
    <string name="ad_caption_1">Precision designed.\nYour drive refined.\nYour day: divine.</string>
    <string name="ad_model_1">RIGA\nSZ-912</string>
    <string name="ad_url_1">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4000/Garrys_Mod/</string>


    <string name="article_headline_1">Unlikely Negotiator Of Peace Garners Ill Will And Distrust As Well As Praise</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_1">Wallace Breen Acknowledges Detractors: \"I\'m Not A Politician, I\'m A Scientist\"</string>

    <string name="article_headline_2">\"Portal\" Storm Continues</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_2">End to Combine Invasion is No Respite, Experts Warn</string>

    <string name="article_headline_3">An Astronomical Downturn</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_3">Historic Bubble Bursts Upon Earth\'s Sudden Surrender to Combine</string>

    // Generated by ChatGPT
    <string name="article_headline_4">Echo of Silence, Across The Northern Wall</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_4">Central Authority Reports Failing Communications: Scientists Advise Isolation During \"Low Resonance\" Phases</string>

    <string name="article_headline_5">Research Bureau Issues New Directive On Containment</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_5">Officials Confirm Restricted Access to All Laboratories, Citing \"Environmental Instability\" and Safety Concerns</string>

    <string name="article_headline_6">Winds Over White Forest Carry the Memory of Dust</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_6">Unverified Reports Indicate Activity Within Abandoned Facilities: \"We Heard Machines Breathing,\" One Witness Claims</string>

    <string name="article_headline_7">\"Portal\" Storm Continues, Despite Government\'s Denials</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_7">The Ministry of Science Describes Disturbances as \"Localized Atmospheric Irregularities\" Affecting Peripheral Zones</string>

    <string name="article_headline_8">Silent Trains Arrive, Carrying No Personnel</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_8">Sources Suggest Automated Convoys Operating Without Oversight, though the Rail Authority Declines to Comment</string>

    <string name="article_headline_9">Wallace Breen Addresses the Council on Order and Trust</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_9">In His Latest Broadcast, He States: \"The Transition Isn\'t Collapse, It’s Control\"</string>

    <string name="article_headline_10">Echo Grid Malfunctions, Signal Becomes Self-Aware</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_10">Operators Report Patterns in the Static that Resemble Speech, yet No Identifiable Source Has Been Found</string>

    <string name="article_headline_11">Beneath The Research Complex, Lights Refuse to Dim</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_11">Maintenance Crews Report Energy Surges at Night, Possibly Linked to Resonant Field Fluctuations in Sublevel D</string>

    <string name="article_headline_12">Synthetic Rain Falls Twice and Never Dries</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_12">Experts Note Atmospheric Layers Behaving Unnaturally: \"Moisture Persists even in Sealed Chambers,\" Says Lead Analyst</string>

    <string name="article_headline_13">Military Units Withdraw From Sector 8, No Explanation Given</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_13">Defense Representatives Refuse to Comment: \"No Statement Until Containment Verified,\" Reports the Press Office</string>

    <string name="article_headline_14">Voice in the Static Claims It\'s Human</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_14">Signal Origin Remains Unknown, yet Phrases Like \"We Are Still Here\" Repeat Across All Channels</string>

    <string name="article_headline_15">\"The Colonies Will Endure,\" Declares Administrative Core</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_15">A Renewed Propaganda Campaign Launches Following Reports of Panic and Resource Shortages in Outer Zones</string>

    <string name="article_headline_16">Black Mesa Echo Detected Beneath Infrastructure Grid</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_16">Technicians Identify Residual Particles Consistent with Experimental Energy Tests Now Reactivating under Stress</string>

    <string name="article_headline_17">Defense Patrols Vanish, Surveillance Continues as Normal</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_17">\"There\'s No Cause for Concern,\" States the Military Office, though Cameras Remain Fixed on Empty Streets</string>

    <string name="article_headline_18">Central Core Emits Harmonic Lull, Calming Personnel</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_18">Medical Divisions Report Reduced Anxiety Patterns: \"It’s Not Influence, It’s Adaptation,\" One Scientist Claims</string>

    <string name="article_headline_19">Breen Issues Statement Amid Rising Doubts, Citing \"Scientific Duty\"</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_19">His Statement Sparks Debate among Staff as Confidence in the Administration Appears Divided</string>

    <string name="article_headline_20">No Birds Remain, Yet the Sky Still Echoes</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_20">Residents Report Phantom Chirps During Dawn Hours, Possibly a Byproduct of Residual Atmospheric Data Loops</string>

    <string name="article_headline_21">Sector 12 Floods with Light, But No Heat</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_21">Officials Attribute the Event to \"Routine Power Tests,\" while Local Instruments Record Radiation Peaks</string>

    <string name="article_headline_22">The Air Speaks Back, Through Broken Intercoms</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_22">Several Facilities Report Unprompted Transmissions Repeating the Phrase: \"We Never Left the Experiment\"</string>

    <string name="article_headline_23">Research Division Unveils \"Peace Enforcement\" Drone Prototype</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_23">Analysts Warn of Self-Learning Algorithms and Non-Lethal Correction Systems Now Active in Test Environments</string>

    <string name="article_headline_24">Old World\'s Currency Discovered in Storage Bunkers</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_24">Economists Dismiss the Find as Symbolic: \"The Only Remaining Value Is Obedience,\" States Market Overseer</string>

    <string name="article_headline_25">Administrator Issues Directive: \"Forget the Mountains\"</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_25">The Order Sparks Confusion as Maps and Geological Records Quietly Begin Vanishing from Public Archives</string>

    <string name="article_headline_26">Civic Broadcast Malfunction Reveals Hidden Frequency</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_26">Engineers Describe the Signal as \"A Mirror Loop,\" Playing Voices of Personnel No Longer Registered</string>

    <string name="article_headline_27">Breen Silent Amid Reports of Internal Division</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_27">Insiders Suggest Conflicting Directives within the Administration, yet Official Channels Insist on Stability</string>

    <string name="article_headline_28">\"Resonance Cascade\" Mention Reappears in Academic Circles</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_28">Researchers Attempt to Reconstruct Lost Documentation, Describing the Event as \"Algorithmic Catastrophe in Slow Motion\"</string>

    <string name="article_headline_29">Scientists Gather in Silence, Facing The Reactor</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_29">The Unofficial Ritual Spreads Across Laboratories: \"We Listen, Because It Listens Back,\" States Participant</string>

    <string name="article_headline_30">Obsolete Terminals Begin Speaking In Unison</string>
    <string name="article_subheadline_30">Technicians Record Messages Referring to \"Arrival Complete,\" Before Systems Power Down without Trace</string>

    <string name="article_1">Decades spent on the cutting edge of theoretical physics put Dr. Wallace Breen in a unique position to negotiate a sweeping multinational surrender to the extraterrestrial invasion force known as \"the Combine.\"\nBut a lifetime ensconced in the bureaucracy of government-funded research-with its security clearances and an emphasis on theory and long-term exploration over urgency and practicality-has left Breen (52) ill-equipped for the moral and political scrutiny his actions have invited</string>
    <string name="article_2">Scientists remain unable to offer any solution to the ongoing \"portal\" storm that has devastated cities worldwide, nor are they any closer to determining how to predict when new portals will appear.\nContrary to early speculation, however, there is a growing consensus that these bizarre weather events, which have deposited aggressive and dangerous creatures at random locations, have not been instigated by the invading \"Combine\" military force. Indeed, the portal creatures and the \"Combine\" appear to be adversaries, according to Nicholas Branken, senior professor of sociocultural anthropology at the University of Helsinki</string>
    <string name="article_3">The soaring markets that had investors riding high mere weeks ago now feel like a distant dream, with the shocking onset of destructive meteorological events and a brutal global war sending stocks plunging.\nMere days later, most stock markets have closed entirely. Markets in New York, Shanghai, Hong Kong, London, and Europe have suspended trading. With communication lines out of Japan largely inactive, the status of Tokyo\'s stock market is currently unknown, but assumed to be closed</string>

    // Generated by ChatGPT
    <string name="article_4">The first static echoes reached the northern boundary before dawn. Observers described the sound as both mechanical and organic, a tone shaped by wind and wire. Reports suggest the wall itself vibrates at irregular intervals, though no official has acknowledged such motion.\nEngineers stationed near the perimeter confirm intermittent pulses recorded by unshielded instruments. The origin remains classified. Some personnel claim to sense faint whispers within the resonance — a language forming, then folding upon itself</string>
    <string name="article_5">The Bureau\'s directive arrived sealed and unsigned, carrying only a numeric cipher. Laboratories now operate under dimmed light, equipment humming with residual heat. No staff are permitted beyond the second corridor without retinal authorization.\nRumors circulate of an uncontained specimen, though leadership insists it\'s theoretical. Most assume the memo refers to cross-field contamination — a concept that grows more literal each day</string>
    <string name="article_6">The wind around the White Forest bends like liquid through magnetic glass. Observers report faint luminescence where mist touches the treetops. Instruments fail to register temperature, suggesting interference from deep-structure emissions.\nLocals describe unseen movements near the abandoned silos — not footsteps, but a sound resembling thought. The forest listens, and occasionally replies</string>
    <string name="article_7">Storm intensity increases despite the silence of officials. Witnesses recount metallic lightning branching across the sky, each flash leaving static in the bloodstream. Many describe the storms as \"structured,\" like deliberate architecture unfolding in air.\nUnconfirmed theories suggest an overlap between magnetic interference and spatial decay. If true, the atmosphere itself is learning to repeat commands</string>
    <string name="article_8">Automated trains continue to arrive, unoccupied and unannounced. Their engines operate on no known timetable, yet motion persists as if guided by a hidden operator. Steel doors remain sealed, emitting low tonal vibrations.\nInspectors report no thermal signatures within the cars, though control panels respond to voice frequencies. The question persists: who is still listening on the other side?</string>
    <string name="article_9">Dr. Breen addressed the Council under flickering lights, the room heavy with interference. He spoke of progress as if reading scripture, eyes fixed on invisible data streams. The word \"trust\" repeated until it lost meaning.\nAfterward, the broadcast looped for eight hours across all civic channels. Listeners claim the tone shifted slightly — his voice no longer matching human cadence</string>
    <string name="article_10">Static across the Echo Grid formed recognizable intervals last night. Operators described the sound as recursive, suggesting self-referential computation within the interference. The grid\'s harmonics began mimicking their own diagnostic tones.\nWhen power was cut, the signal persisted for seventy-two seconds, independent of input. Some technicians believe the static has learned to dream</string>
    <string name="article_11">Below the research complex, generators hum beyond operational tolerance. The light refuses to dim even after full system shutdown. Supervisors insist it\'s a visual anomaly — a trick of persistence.\nYet, shadows behave as if attached to absent bodies. Maintenance staff keep their distance, documenting glow variance while pretending not to count the silhouettes</string>
    <string name="article_12">The artificial rain cycles have exceeded their programmed duration by 43%. Moisture no longer follows gravity, drifting laterally across containment domes. Atmospheric models now resemble abstract art.\nDr. Kreel described the event as \"evaporation with memory.\" Condensation collects on lab windows, forming shapes that mirror unread equations</string>
    <string name="article_13">Military withdrawal from Sector 8 occurred without formal broadcast. Satellite telemetry shows vehicles departing in a spiral formation, though coordinates remain blank. The absence itself seems intentional.\nCivilians report an afterimage of searchlights sweeping empty ground. Official statements classify it as \"routine evacuation,\" a phrase now synonymous with disappearance</string>
    <string name="article_14">A repeating voice emerged from the static bands early this morning. Technicians confirmed its human tone but could not match it to any registry file. The transmission repeats the phrase \"I am awake\" every eleven seconds.\nAttempts to trace its source result only in mirrored echoes. The signal recognizes interruption and adjusts its own frequency — as if unwilling to be silenced</string>
    <string name="article_15">The Administrative Core released a recorded declaration asserting stability across all colonies. The message, though confident, carried distortion resembling suppressed feedback. The word \"endure\" appears seventeen times.\nCitizens report synchronized pauses in power flow during the announcement. Some interpret it as unity — others, as a pulse of warning wrapped in bureaucratic calm</string>
    <string name="article_16">Residual energy beneath the infrastructure grid has begun to fluctuate beyond calibration limits. Technicians found traces of exotic particles once confined to controlled chambers. Instruments misreport mass as probability.\nArchived records reference a \"cascade precursor\" event, classified since the late fiscal cycle. Whatever stirs below, it now hums with administrative indifference</string>
    <string name="article_17">Patrols ceased at dawn, though the surveillance network remained vigilant. Cameras continued to pan and zoom, tracking phantom heat signatures. The system appears self-sustaining — or self-aware.\nPublic statements deny malfunction, insisting on \"adaptive oversight protocols.\" Meanwhile, empty streets remain under perfect observation</string>
    <string name="article_18">Personnel exposed to the Core\'s harmonic lull describe euphoria bordering on sedation. Heart rates fall, and coordinated speech dissolves into murmured agreement. The effect extends through walls, indifferent to shielding.\nMedical reports list improved compliance but reduced autonomy. \"It feels like breathing instruction,\" one subject wrote, before forgetting the words entirely</string>
    <string name="article_19">During a controlled broadcast, Breen addressed accusations with academic precision. He invoked scientific integrity, not politics, yet every word carried the weight of command. The audience responded with algorithmic applause.\nAnalysts note microsecond delays between his speech and transmission, suggesting preprocessing — a voice filtered through approval itself</string>
    <string name="article_20">The absence of birds has not silenced the dawn. Sonic anomalies replicate familiar patterns, though no life remains to produce them. It\'s as if the air replays memory through frequency alone.\nObservers report that each phantom call ends with static, looping indefinitely. The sky hums with nostalgia for organic failure</string>
    <string name="article_21">At precisely 0300 hours, Sector 12 illuminated without heat emission. Radiation counters spiked briefly before resetting to zero. Officials labeled the event \"routine calibration.\"\nWitnesses insist the light carried weight, pressing against surfaces like fog made solid. It faded only when no one remained to see it</string>
    <string name="article_22">Unscheduled transmissions were detected on obsolete intercom networks. The voice, fragmented yet rhythmic, repeated the phrase \"we never left.\" Signal analysis found embedded timestamps decades old.\nAudio experts claim the tone matches archival recordings from early resonance studies. The air, it seems, still remembers its operators</string>
    <string name="article_23">A prototype enforcement drone was unveiled at the Defense Hall with minimal ceremony. The machine hovered soundlessly, emitting faint tonal cues between camera rotations. Its optics reflected every observer simultaneously.\nDevelopers claim the drone interprets hesitation as hostility. Tests are ongoing — though some data logs now redact themselves</string>
    <string name="article_24">Storage crews uncovered sealed crates marked with pre-war emblems. Inside lay faded currency, brittle and meaningless. Economists treated the discovery like an archaeological joke.\nStill, rumors spread that some bills carry warmth when touched. They whisper faintly, promising value to those who already obey</string>
    <string name="article_25">An internal directive ordered the deletion of all mountain references from public record. Geological databases now return blank maps. Employees were told this improves \"clarity of focus.\"\nSeveral archivists reported vertigo when describing elevation. One researcher insisted the horizon feels closer — as if the land obeyed the memo</string>
    <string name="article_26">A civic broadcast interrupted scheduled programming, replacing it with a frequency unassigned to any channel. The content mirrored familiar voices, each sentence folding into the next.\nSpectrographic scans revealed hidden modulation below human hearing. Technicians swear the static whispered their own names, perfectly pronounced</string>
    <string name="article_27">Internal channels report administrative silence, though peripheral chatter grows louder. Rumors of conflicting directives circulate without origin. Each department claims the other is in control.\nThe result is equilibrium through confusion — a balance of noise and obedience. Somewhere, leadership continues speaking, unheard but entirely certain</string>
    <string name="article_28">Academic circles revived discussion of the \"resonance cascade,\" though the term remains forbidden in official documentation. Scholars frame it as theoretical catastrophe, conveniently timeless.\nRecovered fragments of prior simulations show recursive decay — equations devouring themselves. No one admits authorship, yet every institute keeps a copy</string>
    <string name="article_29">At shift change, scientists gathered before the main reactor without speaking. Their presence triggered motion sensors, activating the observation glass. The reactor answered with a low, continuous hum.\nWhen questioned, participants claimed they were waiting for acknowledgment. \"It was listening,\" one said. \"So we waited for it to finish.\"</string>
    <string name="article_30">Decommissioned terminals powered on without external input. Screens displayed strings of coordinates, each corresponding to erased facilities. Operators stood by, unsure whether to document or pray.\nWhen the power grid was cut, the terminals continued transmitting internally. The last visible message read simply: \"Arrival confirmed.\"</string>
</resources>